Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(Episode 3)
Take the medicine.
It smells bitter.
I don't want it.
You're an adult.
Do it yourself.
Situ Xian.
It's been proven that...
you hid the armor in your private army.
I have to go there myself...
to search the warehouse and find evidence.
By the way,
I gave my orchid jade pendant to the Princess of Chu, Lu Zhao.
Take good care of her for me.
When I come back, I'll present her to His Majesty...
as a witness with the evidence.
Sis.
I'll go with you this time.
Something's strange about this.
I'll be careful.
Rest well.
Wait for my return.
I'm not even badly injured.
You don't feel pain.
You don't know how serious these injuries are.
I heard that...
you always say that the medicine's bitter,
and you refuse to take it, right?
Stop being willful.
I'm not being willful.
I'm not a kid anymore.
You're the one who keeps...
Xiao Ren.
I'll take care of this. You stay here.
It's for the greater good.
This is an order.
An order?
You're always giving me orders.
Rest well.
When I come back,
I'll help you with the ointment.
Let's seal the oath with a handshake.
I'll get going then.
By the way,
take the medicine.
I brewed it myself.
All right.
Come back soon.
Okay.
Ms. Lu Zhao. You've been sitting here all night.
Bao Qin.
What about the pill?
I had someone check the pill.
It's not poisonous.
It's even a fine medicine against poison and for clear vision.
This is the Xuntian Sect's secret medicine.
Take it.
See for yourself...
the kind of lie and hell...
you've been living.
Ms. Lu Zhao.
Ms. Lu Zhao!
You can...
see now?
Yes.
“Die a horrible death"
Your Highness.
What's bothering you so much?
You haven't told me.
Xiao Jin Yu has been giving me trouble.
I wonder how much information we have...
on the arms dealers we arrested.
The Xuntian Sect has been relentless.
What if they hurt you?
It doesn't matter.
Judging by the time,
Xiao Jin Yu...
should be dead by now.
The Xuntian Sect without its master...
is nothing.
Your Highness, you're so brave.
I thought that...
the Xuntian Sect is all-powerful.
Yet they were no match for you.
No matter how formidable someone is,
they always have a weakness.
Finding their weak point...
and hitting it with one blow...
isn't difficult.
Then,
Your Highness,
who is your weakness?
Is it Lu Zhao...
or me?
What do you think?
After her birthday banquet,
we'll get the Lu family's assets.
I'll hand Lu Zhao...
over to you.
Then I'll personally...
cut out her baby.
It's a pity...
she's blind.
She can't see...
what her baby...
looks like.
She's blind...
because you poisoned her.
It's obvious that we love each other.
And yet, Zhao Lu relied on the Lu family's wealth...
to marry you.
We have to wait until after her 18th birthday banquet...
before we can get the assets.
I'm forced to hiding like a disgraced rat.
Whenever I think about this,
I want nothing more than to tear her into pieces!
Xue Er.
I like you like this.
You're cruel,
yet filled with desire and ambition.
You're very much like me.
You're nothing like Lu Zhao,
who's so calm...
and boring.
Your Highness.
What's wrong?
Someone was here.
That's impossible.
It's impossible for an outsider...
to come into Zhaoyue Pavilion.
My heart has long been yours.
I vow to walk by your side for life,
to share a bond lasting until our hair turns white,
to raise children in abundance,
and to let our lineage flourish for generations.
From today onward,
you're my wife.
From now on, we'll be together.
We'll spend every day together.
We'll be inseparable.
I love the child very much.
That's because...
it is our first child.
Ms. Lu Zhao.
- Ms. Lu Zhao. - Bao Qin.
Where did you go?
Your clothes are all wet.
Ms. Lu Zhao.
Bao Qin.
- Ms. Lu Zhao. - Get me some...
plain clothes.
I'll leave quietly through the back door.
By the way,
don't alert anyone.
- Now? - Yes.
Ms. Lu Zhao.
What exactly happened?
Situ Xian...
is plotting after the Lu family's property...
and trying to harm me.
I'm going to the Liu manor...
to ask for my father's help.
What?
That's terrible.
Ms. Lu Zhao. I want to go with you.
No.
Listen to me.
King of Chu's manor is powerful.
The Liu manor might not be safe.
Yes, that’s it!
Meet the chief official of Jingzhao.
- Hurry up. - Yes.
Hurry.
It's her.
It seems to be someone from the Xuntian Sect.
Don't you know?
The Xuntian Sect's leader, Xiao Jin Yu,
is dead.
Xiao Jin Yu's dead?
How is that possible?
She was the Emperor's favorite.
The leader of the Xuntian Sect,
Xiao Jin Yu.
It's her.
Judging by the time,
Xiao Jin Yu...
should be dead by now.
The Xuntian Sect without its master...
is nothing.
Situ Xian killed her.
Father.
Lu Zhao.
Aunt.
- Lu Zhao. - You can see!
What's going on?
Father.
Let's talk about my recovery later.
Listen to me.
He's gone too far!
Lu Zhao.
Don't worry.
I’ll see justice done for you.
That's right. Lu Zhao, don't worry.
If Xue Er ever wrongs you,
your father and I will support you.
Master.
The Prince of Chu is here.
Father.
Lu Zhao, don't be afraid.
I'm here for you.
Lu Zhao.
Just as I thought, you can see now.
You couldn't even keep an eye on a blind person.
You almost messed up.
Father.